<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Travel UK - Category - Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/categories/travel-uk/</link><description>Travel UK - Category - Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huatuostudio.github.io/categories/travel-uk/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wondering around London</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140609uk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140609uk/</guid><description>The flight was so long. I kept walking around, eat (funny that I still felt hungry even though I did nothing but sitting there), nap and watch movies:
Bones season 8 - seem them all before, just killing time
Gravity - meh, its okay
The Grand Budapest Hotel - I loved it! It&amp;rsquo;s witty, smart, touching and shows the 1930s Europe
3 days to kill - Kevin Costner looked really old</description></item><item><title>Going to UK</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140605uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140605uk/</guid><description>Overnight in Sydney Cubee Monkey I was still packing when Chris came to pick me up for the airport. :) I definitely started packing early this time but still, it became a last minute thing again. My Qantas flight was late as usual (One day, they will surprise me by being on time). The airport hotel Sydney for a night of transit is as boring as it can be. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get a phone in the room!</description></item><item><title>UK Trip Planning</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140522uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140522uk/</guid><description>Oyster Card My visitor's Oyster Card My visitor&amp;rsquo;s Oyster Card has arrived today! If you want to get an Oyster Card before travelling to London, do a Google search to find an agent in your own country so you can purchase the card in your local currency. Transport for London has more information on the Oyster Card and a list of agents around the world.
London, I will see you soon!</description></item></channel></rss>