<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>road trip - Tag - Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/tags/road-trip/</link><description>road trip - Tag - Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huatuostudio.github.io/tags/road-trip/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canberra</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180309canberra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180309canberra/</guid><description></description></item><item><title>Road Trip Eucumbene</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180427eucumbene/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180427eucumbene/</guid><description></description></item><item><title>Road Trip WA</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20160322roadtripwa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20160322roadtripwa/</guid><description>2016 Easter. Another year and another Easter, time goes so fast. Three of us has decided to take a road trip to the Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Forest Region. We all knew the region pretty well so the trip was roughly planned and the accommodation was booked a few days before the trip.
The Itinerary Itinerary Map Day 1 Leave Perth
Rest at Bunbury (1.5hrs), change driver
Take the National Route 1 from Bunbury to Walpole, rest at Bridgetown and Manjimup</description></item><item><title>Road Trip and Walk Like a Londoner</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140618uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140618uk/</guid><description>I took the train back to London. It was cold comparing with the barmy 22 degrees in Edinburgh a few hours ago. Nevertheless, I was so excited. Here I come, road trip to south England!
Love The Car my rental car is a BMW-M135i First thing first, I needed a car! It was booked a month ago with Avis. The Avis branch can be found inside the St Pancras Station car park.</description></item><item><title>Scotland!</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140612scotland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140612scotland/</guid><description>Edinburgh I love Edinburgh!
Edinburgh The receptionist at the hotel told me that it would be quicker to go to the King&amp;rsquo;s Cross train station by the Tube than taxi. It took me 30min on the Tube from Gloucester Road to the King&amp;rsquo;s Cross train station, not difficult at all.
Not many people were at the Platform 9 3/4 so I had a photo taken in front of it. :) By 9am, there was a long queue of people waiting to take photo there and the station staff had to put signs around to keep things in order.</description></item></channel></rss>