<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Hua Tuo Studio 华拓工作室</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 00:00:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huatuostudio.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Travel Checklist</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20181224travelchecklist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20181224travelchecklist/</guid><description>Life is simpler with a checklist. This is what I use before my travels:
Travel Documents Check all your travel documentations carefully and contact your travel agencies immediately if you have any queries or problems, It’s a good idea to have separate copies of all your documents (including passports) to carry and leave a copy of your itinerary with a relative or friend at home, All names on the booking match passport names of all travellers, Frequent flyer number has been advised and used in all bookings.</description></item><item><title>Travel Bucket List</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180629travelbucketlist/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180629travelbucketlist/</guid><description>Soak in the Pamukkale thermal pools, Turkey
Explore the fascinating Salar de Uyuni salt flats, Bolivia
Find paradise on Palawan Island, the Philippines
See the spectacular Northern Lights
Discover the “temple that is a city” at Angkor Wat in Cambodia
Scale Japan’s highest peak, Mount Fuji
Take a trip into the wilderness on an African safari
Ascend the arch of Sydney Harbour Bridge My story here
Trek the Inca Trail to Machu Picchu</description></item><item><title>La Petite France</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180513lapetitefrance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180513lapetitefrance/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m joining a 10 days La Petite France trip with Albatross Tours. So excited!!! 😻😻😻
Tour Overview Sleep in a picturesque château in the Loire Valley, walk amongst the flowers of Monet’s Gardens and Château Villandry and dine on exquisite seafood in the ‘pirate town’ of St Malo. Stand on the Normandy beaches, visit magnificent Mont-Saint-Michel and sip Benedictine in a palace! C’est magnifique…
Tour Map Highlights Stay 3 nights on the verdant Normandy Coast in the classic seaside resort of Cabourg</description></item><item><title>Canberra</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180309canberra/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180309canberra/</guid><description></description></item><item><title>Road Trip Eucumbene</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180427eucumbene/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20180427eucumbene/</guid><description></description></item><item><title>Road Trip WA</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20160322roadtripwa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20160322roadtripwa/</guid><description>2016 Easter. Another year and another Easter, time goes so fast. Three of us has decided to take a road trip to the Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Forest Region. We all knew the region pretty well so the trip was roughly planned and the accommodation was booked a few days before the trip.
The Itinerary Itinerary Map Day 1 Leave Perth
Rest at Bunbury (1.5hrs), change driver
Take the National Route 1 from Bunbury to Walpole, rest at Bridgetown and Manjimup</description></item><item><title>Taiwan Impression</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20150405taiwan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20150405taiwan/</guid><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="sleepless-in-hong-kong">Sleepless In Hong Kong</h2>
<p>Chinese say that 4 is not a lucky number, clearly 04/04 is worse and it was totally true - I&rsquo;ve had a terrible run today! 😢</p>
<p>The flight from Sydney to Hong Kong was delayed and the connecting flight from Hong Kong to Taipei left without me. :( Apparently, it was also the last flight for the day to fly over the channel. I was stranded in Hong Kong for the night with just my passport and a wallet in my bag. Note to self, I should always put an extra pair of undies in my carry on!</p>
<p>This is part of the fun of traveling - dealing with problems on the go, regardless how well I planned for weeks before the trip. :) I actually have never been left stranded with no luggage before. Sigh, there is always a first hey. I started to wonder what else could go wrong now.</p>
<p></p>
<p>After some negotiation, the airline put me in the <a href="http://www.marriott.com/hotels/travel/hkgap-hong-kong-skycity-marriott-hotel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Hong Kong SkyCity Marriott Hotel</a>. I&rsquo;d gave it 5 stars for the facility and the service! It was 12am when I checked in and I have to get up in 5 hours. I planned to watch some movies but after a hot shower, I pretty much passed out. 😃</p>]]></description></item><item><title>RSPCA Pet Quiz Website</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140905petquiz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20140905petquiz/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m giving myself a 🌟 for finishing a little volunteer project for RSPCA (AU) ACT. :-)
The idea is to create a website that contains a Pet Quiz where people answer a few questions to find out what kind of pet is the best suitable for them. The logic for the website is pretty simple so I kept the design simple and clean too. The website is going to be used on iPads in RSPCA ACT&amp;rsquo;s booth at this year&amp;rsquo;s Florida (URL: http://rspcapetquiz.</description></item><item><title>How To Make Japanese Pickled Ginger</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20130430japanesepickledginger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20130430japanesepickledginger/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s all over the net at the moment - ginger is the essential healthy power food! I don&amp;rsquo;t put a lot of ginger in my cooking but I love to eat Japanese pickled ginger from time to time. This is a recipe I&amp;rsquo;ve been using. The result was great, even mum gave it a thumbs up. Here is the VERY simple recipe on how to make Janpanese pickled ginger:
Japanese Pickled Ginger Recipe My pickled ginger.</description></item><item><title>Sydney Harbour Bridge Climb</title><link>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20130406harbourbridge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><author>@huatuostudio</author><guid>https://huatuostudio.github.io/20130406harbourbridge/</guid><description>The Experience John has bought me a ticket for a full 3 hours of Sydney Harbour Bridge Climb for my birthday this year (thank you John!! 💕 ). I have to say that I have always thought the bridge climb is an overpriced tourist thing. Why would I ever do that if I live here?! :) Nevertheless, I was excited to wake up at 3am to get ready for the bridge climb.</description></item></channel></rss>